Welcome to this short course on
LangChain for large
language model application
development.
By prompting an LLM
or large language model,
it is now possible
to develop AI applications
much faster than ever before.
But an application
can require prompting
an LLM multiple times and parsing
its output, and so there's
a lot of glue code
that needs to be written.
LangChain, created by Harrison
Chase makes this
development process much easier. I'm
thrilled to have Harrison here, who
had built this short course in
collaboration with DeepLearning.ai to
teach how to use this amazing tool.
Thanks for having me. I'm
really excited to be here. LangChain
started as an open source framework
for building LLM
applications. It came about when
I was talking to a bunch
of folks in the field who
were building more
complex applications and
saw some common abstractions in terms
of how they were being developed.
And we've been really thrilled at
the community adoption of
LangChain so far.
And so look forward
to sharing it with
everyone here and look
forward to seeing what
people build with it.
And in fact, as a sign of LangChain's
momentum, not
only does it have numerous users, but
there are also many
hundreds of contributors to
the open source, and this has been
instrumental for its
rapid rate of development. This
team really ships code and features
at an amazing pace.
So hopefully,
after this short course, you'll
be able to quickly put together
some really cool
applications using LangChain, and
who knows, maybe
you even decide to
contribute back to the
open source LangChain effort.
LangChain is an
open source development
framework for building
LLM applications.
We have two different packages,
a Python one and a JavaScript one.
They're focused on composition
and modularity. So
they have a lot
of individual components that
can be used in
conjunction with each other
or by themselves. And so that's one
of the key value adds. And then
the other key value add is a bunch
of different use cases. So chains
of ways of combining
these modular components into
more end-to-end applications making it
very easy to get
started with those use
cases. In this class, we'll
cover the common components of LangChain. So
we'll talk about models.
We'll talk about prompts, which are how
you get models to
do useful and interesting things.
We'll talk about indexes, which
are ways of ingesting
data so that you
can combine it with models. And
then we'll talk about chains, which are
more end-to-end use cases along
with agents, which are a very
exciting type of end-to-end use case which uses
the model as a reasoning engine.
We're also grateful to Ankush Gola, who
is a co-founder of LangChain alongside Harrison
Chase, for also
putting a lot of thought into
these materials and
helping with the
creation of this short course.
And on the DeepLearning.AI side, Geoff
Ludwig, Eddy Shyu, and
Diala Ezzeddine have
also contributed to
these materials.
And so with that, let's
go on to the next video, where we'll learn
about LangChain's models, prompts, and parsers.